感谢您乘坐捷蓝航空
Thank you for flying JetBlue.
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯
Welcome to Las Vegas.
给你  给你
Here you go, here you go.
办得真快
That was quick.
尊贵级别客户无需排队
You skip the line when you're on the excelsior level.
三个房间挨在一起  顶层
Three rooms adjoing, top floor.
银色的  好漂亮
Silver, pretty.
是白金的  所以别拿着到处挥
Platinum, so don't wave that around everywhere.
别人会嫉妒的
People'll get jealous.
或许挥一下也无妨
Maybe wa it around a little.
我朋友伯特・坦纳经营这个酒店
My friend Burt Tanner runs the hotel.
他免费提供给我们几间房
He comped us a few rooms
因为我们卖给他几组橱柜
because we sold him some closets
安装在他的那些土豪套房里
for his high-roller suites.
斑纹木  可加温的袜子抽屉
Zebrawood, heated sock drawer,
精致做工
the works.
您好  奢华浴室
Hey, luxury bathroom,
正是在下  卑微的橱柜
it's me, lowly closet.
小心点
Watch your back.
米奇尔
Mitchell?
朗翰姆
Langham?
小卡
Hey, Cam,
这是朗翰姆和蒂姆
I-it's Langham and Tim!
你们在这儿干什么
What are you boys doing here?
举行我们的告别单身派对
Bachelor-party weekend.
我们要在六月结婚了
We're getting married in June.
什么
What?
我们很想邀请你们的
Oh, we really wanted to invite you,
但是蒂姆的家庭成员太多
but Tim's family is huge --
没事的  我们要在五月结婚
Relax. We're getting married in May
也没邀请你们  所以
and you're not coming, so...
米奇尔
Mitchell.
真好  我们现在都看开了
Oh, look at us moving on.
就像你从未在我跟你说我爱你的
It's almost like you never dumped me in an e-mail
第二天早晨用一封邮件把我甩了
the morning after I told you that I loved you.
我得辩解一下  邮件
Well, y-- in my defense, e-mail --
在那时候还是新鲜玩意
it was new back then...
而且还很难说
...and it was still a blurry line
用什么方式是合适的
as to what was appropriate and...
我们这周末非常忙
Well, we have a pretty packed weekend.
没错  如果你们有时间
Oh, we do,but if you guys have some time,
这是我们的日程表
here's our itinerary.
-好的  -一起来玩吧
- Okay.  - Come play.
-没问题  -玩得开心  再见
- Oh, yeah.  - Fun. Bye.
-恭喜你们  -谢谢
- You guys, congratulations.   - Thank you.
天啊
Oh, my gosh,
一个真正的同性恋日程
an actual gay agenda.
[Gay agenda指为维护同性恋权益做出的种种努力]
看来这些天不会经常看到你们两个了
Looks like we're not gonna see much of you two this trip.
-不  -不会不会
- No. - No, no.
我们是不会参加这上面的任何活动的
We are not participating in any of this.
他们对于单身派对很挑剔的
They're very judgy about bachelor parties.
我提出要帮他们办
I offered to throw them one,
结果被讲了一通大道理
and I got a whole lecture.
我们已经40了  还有个孩子
We're 40. We have a child.
我们已经在一起十年了
We've been together for 10 years.
又来了
That's the one.
我们已经不是那样的人了
It's just not who we are anymore.
听听这个  "香蕉小屋泳池派对"
Listen to this -- "Bananas and cabanas pool party."
-天啊  小卡  -没错
- Oh, Cam.  - Yeah.
"最具创意泳装获得者
"Most creative speedo
将赢得苏格兰短裙士兵欢乐秀的门票"
wins tickets to the kilty pleasures."
-不要  -得了吧
- No!  - Please.
什么是苏格兰短裙士兵欢乐秀
What is the kilty pleasures?
这个
This.
我们将在水疗室维护我们的尊严  谢谢
We will be maintaining our dignity in the spa, thank you.
拜托
I mean, come on,
哪有苏格兰人晒到这么黑的
have you ever seen a scottish person this tan?
我光看着都觉得难为情
I'm embarrassed even looking at it.
那就别看了
Then stop.
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
翻译：慕秋雪  四方虾  王大可  小花豆  姚小事儿  丁小七
时间轴：浓子   校对：olivia_xuxu   后期&总监：瓜瓜
摩  登
家  庭
第五季 第十八集
那个加温抽屉实在太好使了
Whoa, that warmer drawer really works.
感觉像是我妈又一次抱着我的脚
It's like my mom's hugging my feet again.
我要去购物了
I'm gonna go do some shopping.
那我们待会儿再碰头
Oh, well, maybe we'll catch up later.
不用了  你忙你的
No, you have your day,
我忙我的
I'll have mine.
那五点在酒吧见好吗
Well, how 'bout the bar at like 5:00?
好的
Sure.
她在跟我冷战
She was icing me,
但是我罪有应得
but I deserved it.
我平生第一次
For the first time in my whole life,
忽视了她
I was neglecting her.
我受邀去参加一个
I'd been invited to audition
拉斯维加斯秘密魔法学会的面试
for a secret magic society in Las Vegas,
但当我没日没夜地彩排时
but in all my rehearsals,
就忽略了克莱尔的存在
I'd paid no attention to Claire.
我甚至有一次把她单独留在了影院
I even left her alone in a movie theater once.
大事不妙
Oh, no.
我让菲尔以为我还在生他的气
I let Phil think I was still mad at him
因为我需要点私人时间
because I needed a little time to myself.
快到老娘怀里  太棒了
Come to mama! Yeah!
几年前  菲尔和我攒了些钱
Years ago, Phil and I put aside money
为了在结婚25年纪念日出去旅行
for a trip on our 25th anniversary,
但有个周末我和女朋友们
but I lost that money on
去赌城把钱输光了
a girls' weekend in vegas.
从那时起  我就在执行一个秘密任务
Since then, I've been on a secret mission
为了把钱赢回来
to win that money back,
如果这周末一切顺利的话
and if things go well this weekend,
我就能回本了
I am even.
拉斯维加斯  你有个赌博问题
Vegas, you have a gambling problem,
她的名字就叫克莱尔
and her name is Claire.
咚咚咚
Knockity-knock-knock.
我猜您是邓菲先生吧
Mr. Dunphy, I presume?
是的  你好
Yes. Who-- hi.
我叫莱斯利・希金斯
I'm Leslie Higgins
在我家乡这是个男孩名
it's a boy's name where I'm from.
我是您的管家
I'm your butler.
管家啊  真好
Oh. Butler. Cool.
是的  作为尊贵客人
Yes. As an excelsior guest,
我24小时随时待命为您服务
uh, I'm at your beck and call 24/7.
任何事情  大事小情  我都能
Anything you need, big or small, I can
先生  我能不能接下来
Can I just segue, sir,
向您介绍我会如何保护您的隐私
to the importance of discretion in my job?
我就把这些放在...
I'll just pop those --
不不不  不用管了
Oh, no, no, no. Never mind those.
- 如您所愿   - 我等下有个约会要用到它
- As you wish.   - They're for an appointment I have later.
你知道的越少越好
The less you know about that, the better.
实在非常抱歉  先生
A myriad of apologies, sir.
如果没有别的事...
If there's nothing else...
等下
Oh, hang on.
你知道哪儿能洗披肩吗
Actually, do you know where I can get a cape laundered?
歌剧还是那种超级英雄披肩
Opera or superhero?
不便透露
I'd rather not say.
这个问题越线了
I overstepped the mark by asking.
我能不能小小地介绍下
Uh, could I just, uh, quickly point out
我们的豪华沐浴服务  先生
our luxury bath service, sir?
我们提供五种超级豪华沐浴套餐
We have five outrageously decadent baths
您若需要我马上就能为您准备好
that I can prepare for you at a moment's notice.
不过需要说明的是
Uh, I should just point out, though,
"法老的幻想"套餐需要花费一点时间
that our Pharaoh's Fantasy does take a dash longer,
因为我们的努比亚人演员不常驻酒店
normally, because our Nubian lives off-site.
如果没有别的吩咐
Um...if there's nothing else,
我就帮您把箱子放好
I'll just help you with your case.
不
Uh, no, uh --
-我自己来吧  -好的
- I'll get that.  - Yeah.
好了  谢谢
All right. Thank you.
-我爱死黄瓜水了  -我知道
- I love cucumber water.  - I know.
-如果我是总统  -我知道我知道
- If I were president   - I know, I know.
就在水库里装满黄瓜
Cucumbers in the reservoirs.
巨大的黄瓜
Giant cucumbers.
普里契特先生
Mr. Pritchett?
是的
Yes, hi.
好了  90分钟后见
All right, I'll see you in 90 minutes.
-好好享受  -谢谢
- Enjoy.   - Thank you.
塔克先生
Mr. Tucker?
有几位客人决定不去布兰妮的演唱会了
We had a few no-shows for the Britney concert, so...
我要一张  谢谢
One, please.
那米奇尔呢
Uh, what about Mitchell?
这里是赌城  他不需要知道我在做什么
It's Vegas -- he doesn't need to know what I'm doing.
我也不需要知道他在做什么
I don't need to know what he's doing.
所以如果你见到他
So if you see him,
也别告诉他我在做什么
maybe don't mention what I'm doing.
了解
Oh. Understood.
你有挨着走廊的座位吗
So, do you have anything on the aisle?
哪位
Yeah?
拉斯普京的达马西亚人淹死在伏尔加河
Rasputin's Dalmatian drowned in the Volga.
我以为他对狗过敏
I thought he was allergic to dogs.
你想的是梅林
You're thinking of Merlin.
应该是花生
And it was peanuts.
大家好
Okay, everybody.
我们来了个客人
We have a visitor.
欢迎菲尔・邓菲
Welcome Phil Dunphy.
你好  菲尔
Hey, Phil.
你好  能来到这儿很荣幸
Hey. I'm so honored to be here.
你们也许认识我的用户名
You may recognize my -- my screen name,
天灵地灵邓菲17
Abracadunphy17.
那是你吗
That's you?
你经常在半夜上线
You're up in the middle of the night a lot.
我太太睡觉磨牙
My wife grinds her teeth.
但让我给你们讲另一个故事吧
But let me tell you another story.
是关于变形奇迹的
It's about the miracle of metamorphosis.
-菲尔  -人们说唯一不变的是变化
- Uh, Phil   - They say the only constant is change --
菲尔  我们等下再看你的表演
Phil, we're gonna get to your trick in just a minute.
不好意思
Oh. I'm sorry.
有点小激动了
Got a little excited there.
博客界地下魔术师中的英雄们
The heroes of the underground-magic blogosphere --
"闪火纸"菲内利  凯撒杀手  小孩
"Flashpaper" Finelli, Kaiser Mayhem, the Kid.
想想看
When you think about it,
能同时见到活生生的他们简直不可思议
it's crazy they're all alive at the same time.
杰  我觉得有点冷
Jay, I'm feeling a little cold.
也许我该买条围巾
Maybe I should buy a scarf.
当然  买两条
Sure, get a couple of 'em.
怎么  我知道这有点奢侈
Why, I know it's a little extravagant,
但我们现在是尊贵客人了
but we're excelsior now --
当然要有尊贵的样子
might as well look it.
很多年前  杰在拉斯维杰斯时
Many years ago, when Jay was in Las Vegas,
买了巴克利
he bought Barkley,
那个狗管家
the doggy butler.
我恨死巴克利了
I hate Barkley.
我知道如果杰看到丽巴卡
I knew if Jay saw Rebarka,
他也会想买的
he would want her too.
是的  那是她的名字  丽巴卡
Yeah, that's her name -- Rebarka.
但是  那个
Uh, but, uh -- you know,
如果我们要去赌博
if we're going to gamble,
也许我需要那件幸运毛衣
maybe I need my lucky sweater.
你能去房间里帮我拿来吗
Can you go and get it in the room?
你怎么还有幸运毛衣
Who has a lucky sweater?
你看超级杯赛时还穿两只不一样的鞋呢
You wore two different shoes to watch the Super Bowl.
好吧
Fine.
别  杰
No, Jay!
走那边
Other way.
我喜欢那边
I like that way.
不好意思先生  这是私人电梯
Sorry, sir. This is a private elevator.
不用道歉
No need to apologize.
我很高兴你业务熟练
I'm glad you're on top of this stuff.
您的卡只能到达尊贵客户层
That's only for the excelsior level.
这架电梯是去顶层的
This elevator goes to the top floor.
我以为尊贵级别就是顶层  62层
I thought excelsior was the top -- 62.
曼德勒海湾酒店有63层
Mandalay Bay has 63 floors.
顶层是高级尊贵层
Top floor is excelsior plus.
等等  他们可以上去吗
Wait, they're allowed up there?
他们穿的是粗布工作服啊
They're wearing dungarees.
[曼德勒海湾酒店]
61  62  63层
61, 62...63!
你妹
Son of a bitch!
拜托  给我来个八
Come on, let me see an eight.
我想要个八
I want to see an eight.
七
Seven out.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们下把会赢的  宝贝
We'll get 'em next time, baby.
克莱尔  把你的钥匙给我
Claire. Give me your key.
我有个东西得记在你房间的账上
I need to charge something to your room.
等一下
Hang on a second.
四  点数是四
Four. Point is four.
好的  赌四和五在C和E上
Okay, odds on four and a five each on "C" And "E."
你刚才说什么
What are you talking about?
是巴克利的女款
It's the lady version of Barkley.
我得预订上
I have to put it on hold
这样杰就算看到也买不到了
so that Jay, if he sees it, he can't buy it,
然后走时我会把帐销掉的
and then I will cancel the charge before we leave.
赢家是  四  真不易
Winner-- four the hard way!
太棒了  终于押上了
Oh, yes! Finally!
能给我钥匙吗
Can I have the key?
不  亲爱的  你哪都别去
Oh, no, honey. You're not going anywhere.
你是我的幸运女神
You're my good-luck charm.
吹口气  美女
Give these a blow, beautiful.
按摩得怎么样
And how was your massage?
太放
So re--
太放松了
So, so relaxing.
抱歉我的按摩师一直在放恩雅的音乐
Sorry, my masseuse was blasting the Enya.
你接下来想干点什么呢
So, what are you gonna do next?
泡个澡
A long soak?
还是蒸个桑拿
A long sauna?
我想蒸桑拿
I think a sauna.
是吗  我想泡个澡
Yeah, I think I'm gonna do a soak.
泡澡也不错
Ooh, a soak does sound nice.
要不我还是蒸桑拿吧
Maybe I'll do a sauna.
你脸上那是亮粉吗
Is that-- is that glitter on your face?
是啊  我的按摩师可能夜间兼职
Yeah, I think my masseuse might moonlight.
拉斯维加斯嘛
Vegas.
-好吧  一小时后见  -好的
- All right, I'll see you in an hour.  - Okay. Yeah.
好好享受吧
Enjoy it. Really have fun.
放松  米奇尔
Relax, Mitchell.
菲尔  该你了
Phil, you're up.
好的
Okay.
化茧成蝶的奇迹
The miracle... of metamorphosis.
人们说唯一不变的是变化
They say the only constant is change.
然而一切都将变  不同
Well, all of that is about to ch-- be different.
注意这只是个粗麻袋
Note the simple burlap sack,
家里随意都能找到
the kind you'd find in any home.
可以麻烦你帮我一下吗
If you'd be so kind as to assist me,
孩子
the-- the-- the Kid,
我要尽力证明一些变化是漫长的
I'll endeavor to prove that some change is glacial,
而有一些变化是瞬间的
while some change is instantaneous.
现在麻烦你把粗麻袋提起来
Now, if you'd be so kind as to raise the simple burlap sack
提过我的头  在我手腕处收紧
above my head and pinch my wrists.
注意时间是4点02分
You'll note, the clock says exactly 4:02.
我的表是3点15
I have 3:15.
我的是6点35
Yeah, I have 6:35.
凯撒杀手
Kaiser Mayhem!
是我干的
It's what I do.
等等  已经5点20了吗
Wait, it's 5:20?
我得给我太太打个电话
I actually have to call my wife.
不行  菲尔  不能在魔术半途停下来
Oh, no, Phil, you can't just stop in the middle of a trick.
这是基本的行规
That's a cardinal rule.
各位  这是紧急情况
Guys, it's an emergency.
别跟我说你们从未
Don't tell me you've never
不得不停下来打给另一半
had to call your spouse.
你们  你们会找到另一半的
Oh...there's-- there's people for you.
拜托  克莱尔  快接啊
Come on, Claire. Please pick up.
又是这位女士赢了
And the lady wins again.
很好  很好
Yes! Yes!
我做到了  我做到了
I did it! I did it!
我做到了  我赢回了我的钱
I did it! I won back my money.
认输吧  豪斯
Oh, suck it, the house.
克莱尔  钥匙
Claire, the key.
好的  好的  给你
Yeah, okay, here you go.
给自己买点闪闪的东西吧
And, hey, buy yourself something sparkly.
歌洛莉亚  我们上面还有一层
Gloria, there's a floor above us.
-什么  -是啊  我也很震惊
- What?!   - I know. It threw me, too.
高级尊贵层
Excelsior plus.
但对于那层的人来说
But to the people on that floor,
我们就是次级豪华
we're excelsior minus.
那上面有什么呢
Mm, what is up there?
得拿黑卡才能进入
You need a black card to get in.
可我们只有这破烂银卡
All we've got is this stupid silver one.
我还以为是铂金卡呢
Oh, I thought it was platinum.
这是垃圾
It's crap.
为什么
Uh, why-
你何不打给你的朋友伯特
why don't you call your friend Burt
跟他说我们需要黑卡呢
and tell him that we need the black card?
因为他不是我的朋友
Because he's not my friend.
我都没见过他
I never really even met him.
我可能就在一次电话会议上听到过他咳嗽
I think I heard him cough one time on a conference call.
不知道他为什么要这么对我
I don't know why he would treat me this way.
-不是吧  -怎么了
- Oh, come on!   - What?
不是吧  你是杰・普里契特
Oh, come on! You're Jay Pritchett!
你要找到你的朋友伯特
You're gonna find your friend Burt
告诉他你是谁
and tell him who you are,
你会要到黑卡
and you're gonna get the black card,
因为当你决定做一件事
because when you set your mind on something,
没人能阻止你
nobody can stop you!
没错
Right!
等等
Wait!
从那边走
Go that way.
不好意思
Excuse me,
橱窗里那只狗多少钱
how much is that doggy in the window?
我终于从赌城手里拿回了属于我的东西
I had finally taken back from Vegas what Vegas took from me.
那种满足感很难形容
That's a feeling of satisfaction I can't describe...
因为没持续太久
Because it didn't last very long.
-克莱尔  -什么事
- Oh, hey, Claire.  - Yeah?
-你看到小卡了吗  -没有
- Have you seen Cam?  - No.
我们应该呆在一个地方好让他找到我们
Although...we should stay in one place so he can find us.
找个二十一点牌桌怎么样
How about a blackjack table?
不  我刚做完按摩和桑拿  很困
Oh, no, I'm really worn out from my massage, the sauna...
排出了很多毒素
It was just-- it was a lot of detoxing.
知道你需要什么吗
You know what you need?
-来点毒素  -不
- Some toxing.  - No.
玩几盘二十一点  再喝几杯龙舌兰
Hand of blackjack, couple of tequilas.
来嘛  可好玩了  快去
Come on, it'll be fun. Do it.
你听起来就像小时候
You sound just like the kid who bullied me
逼我抽第一支烟那个人
into smoking my first cigarette.
也许这次你不会告发我
Maybe this time you won't tell on me.
-继续拿牌  -好
- And then hit.  - Yes.
继续拿牌  然后停牌
And then hit. And then stay.
-我知道怎么玩  -好吧
- I know. I have it.   - Okay.
十八点  十九点  十八点
18, 19, 18.
你赢面很大
You are in a great position right now.
庄家是二十一点
Oh, the dealer has 21.
她的牌更好
Hers is better.
真不好意思  米奇尔
I am so sorry, Mitchell.
可我保证我们刚刚每一步都做对了
I promise you, we did everything right.
别太不爽
Don't be mad.
-我没有不爽  -真的吗
- I'm not mad.  - Really?
我只是  只是太激动了
T-that was -- that was thrilling. I'm...
-我心跳加快了  -是吧  好玩吧
- My pulse is racing.  - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-真谢谢你让我玩这个  -那当然
- Thank you so much for making me do this.   - Yeah.
我要再玩一局
I'm going to play another hand.
我们要再玩一局
We're going to play another hand.
不是我们  是我
No, alone.
-我不带你玩  霉运走开  -真的吗
- Not with you. You're bad luck.   - Really?
走远一点
Go -- far.
我一摆脱她
The minute I got rid of her,
就开始一路狂赢
I couldn't lose.
赌钱真好玩
Oh, gambling's fun.
还很简单
And easy.
你好  土豪哥
Hey, big spender.
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
赌博  我现在是个赌徒
Gambling. I'm a gambler now.
-本性暴露了啊  -没错
- Look at you, letting loose.   - Yeah.
我想通了
Yeah, I guess I figure
不管在赌城玩得多疯
whatever mischief one might get into in Vegas
出了赌城就都不存在了
kind of remains here within the limits of the city, you know?
-这想法很酷  -是吧
- That's a cool way to think about it.  - Yeah.
我真的很高兴在这里碰到你
You know, I'm really glad that you came over here.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why is that?
我一直很遗憾
Well, I always hated the way
我们当年结束得不太愉快
that things ended between us, you know?
说不定我们现在可以尝试好好相处
Maybe now we can go out on a better note.
-那样很好  -没错
- That's nice.   - Yeah.
天啊
Oh -- oh, my god!
6-2-3-3  这是我的房号
6-2-3-3, that's -- that's my room number.
要牌
Huh. Um, hit me.
七
Seven!
是二十一点
That's 21, huh?
太棒了
Yes! Yeah! Ah!
瞧瞧  你真厉害
Whoa, check you out.
我觉得今晚是我的幸运之夜
I guess tonight's my night to get lucky.
我也觉得
I would say.
-给你  -谢谢
- Here you are. - Thank you.
-我们说不定很快就会再见面  -好
- Maybe I will run into you again, huh?   - Okay.
那个  你
Oh, you...
这里有2140美金  希金斯
There are $2140, Higgins,
天降横财  天降横财
for nothing -- nothing!
我要做点疯狂的事
I want to do something crazy.
我要订一个沐浴套餐
Okay, I'm gonna order a bath.
先生  我觉得您好像癫狂了
Sir, it seems to me like you've gone mad.
要的就是这个效果
Okay, this is what I want.
我想来点浪漫
I want something romantic,
但又带点危险的
but also a little dangerous.
浪漫又危险
Romantic, dangerous --
如果让我建议的话  电子乐沐浴怎么样
might I suggest, sir, the techno bath?
您的心脏将和贝司一起脉动
Your heart will throb with the bass
您的双眼将享受一场超高端激光秀
while your eyes take in an off-the-scale laser light show
一切都在最私密的贵宾场所进行
from that most intimate of V.I.P. arenas
也就是您自己的浴缸
-- your own tub.
好  就要那个了
Okay. I want that.
正是我想要的
That's what I want.
我觉着小红帽实际上是只大坏狼
Me thinks the little red riding hood may be a big, bad wolf.
我很快就带着需要的东西回来
I'll be back shortly with supplies.
好
Okay!
邓菲先生  今晚
Ah, Mr. Dunphy! How are...
过得怎么样
...we this evening?
不怎么样
Not so good.
跟我老婆起了点摩擦
I'm in a tight spot with my lady.
你知道什么能有所帮助吗
You know what might help?
不如来一个那种  豪华沐浴套餐
One of those -- one of those luxury baths.
将她置于温暖的泡澡水当中
Ah, get yourself out of some hot water
以解救自己于水深火热之中
by getting her into some.
太棒了
Wow, so good.
我的建议是麦可・布雷泡泡浴
Might I suggest the Michael Buble Bath?
你简直会读心术
You are a mind reader.
我不会读心术  先生
I'm not a mind reader, sir.
我只是从九十年代起
I've just been in the bath-buttling business
就干沐浴管家这行了
since the early '90s,
尽管我看起来很年轻
despite my fresh face.
所以我很了解什么情况选什么套餐
So I tend to know what these situations need.
-我这就去放水  -如您所愿
- I'll get the water going. - As you wish.
反正价格都一样
Same price either way.
伯特说他马上就过来
Burt says he's gonna be here any minute.
我们一定要好好招待他
We got to really lay it on for this guy --
最好的苏格兰威士忌  穿得性感点
best scotch, put on something sexy.
我  我有个好主意
I... have a great idea!
雪茄
Cigars!
伯特那种男人一定会喜欢上好的雪茄
A man like Burt appreciates a good cigar.
这主意不错
Good thinking!
当然要是在楼上  管家早就来了
Of course, upstairs, the butler would be here already.
我告诉你吧
I'm telling you,
我们这就跟睡在地下室一样
we might as well be sleeping in the basement.
我说的是"存"货不是"送"货
I said hold it, not deliver it!
好吧  这边
Okay, there.
过来这里
Come here.
好好待在克莱尔的屋子里
Stay in Claire's room.
亲爱的  我在浴室里呢
Hey, honey. I'm in the bathroom.
亲爱的
Honey?
好吧  我知道我错了
Okay, I-I know I messed up,
但坐好  我为你准备了惊喜
But sit tight -- I got a little surprise for you.
希金斯  你有空吗
Higgins, you got a minute?
一小时里有60分钟有空
60 an hour.
全都由您支配  先生
They all belong to you, sir.
我需要尽快搞一些高级雪茄
I need a couple of primo cigars, A.S.A.P.
我不在乎它们是如何到达我们国家的
I'm not a stickler for how they got in the country.
我还在等一瓶特制苏格兰威士忌
I'm also expecting a special Scotch delivery.
还需要刮个胡子
I need a shave.
我不能这样去见伯特
Burt can't see me like this.
很遗憾  剃须管家只在
Unfortunately, the shaving butlers are all --
我知道  只有高级尊贵层有
I know, excelsior plus.
-方便进来吗  -方便
- Are you decent?   - I am.
很快就不方便了哦
Well, not for long.
我的爱人随时就要回来了
My partner should be here any minute.
先生  是我的原因吗
Is it me, sir,
还是这空气中本就充满了情爱的氛围
or is the air positively fizzing with erotic anticipation?
是啊
Yeah.
我忘了拿冰块
Oh, I forgot the ice.
我这就去拿
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna get it.
怎么能让您去呢
Oh, I couldn't ask you to do that.
不  没关系的
No, not a problem.
那好吧
As you wish.
反正都是一样的价格
Same price either way.
不好意思
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
我想找米奇尔
I-I'm looking for Mitchell.
是的  他正在等您
Oh, yeah, he's expecting you.
事实上  他让我帮两位准备了沐浴
In fact, he's asked me to draw the two of you a bath.
-太疯狂了  -是啊
- This is crazy.   - Yeah.
我觉得这正是他的本意
I believe that's the plan.
请尽情享受
Enjoy.
谢谢
Thank you.
太好了  你回来了
Oh, good. You're back.
克莱尔看起来心情如何
How's Claire seem?
什么
I'm sorry?
你在外面肯定碰到她了吧  她生气了吗
You must have seen her out there. Is she mad?
她在干什么
W-what's she doing?
她在除尘  先生
Uh, she's dusting, sir.
她生气时总是喜欢打扫
Oh, she always cleans when she's mad.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor --
给她拿杯饮料
Bring her a drink
让她在沙发上休息一下
and tell her to get comfortable on the couch.
她可以趴上家具是吧
She's -- she's allowed on the furniture, is she?
她是我妻子
She's my wife.
太好了  我正在找你
Oh, good! I've been looking for you.
你应该正在找一个
Well, you should have been looking for somebody
正在找你的人
who was looking for you,
因为那正是我在做的事
because that's what I was doing.
快来  我给你准备了惊喜
Come on, I have a surprise for you.
是啊  我一直在想
Yeah, I-I've been thinking
我们不能总是这么紧张又保守
we need to stop being so uptight.
我们可是在赌城啊
We are in Vegas.
我们来找点乐子吧
Let's have a little fun.
我得努力适应一下  但好吧
Well, I'll have to wrap my head around that, but okay.
我正好知道要如何开始
Now, I have just the way to kick it off --
这件事我们可以一起做
something we could do together.
虽然尺度有点大
It's a little extreme,
-但我觉得那正是我们需要的  -好吧
- but I think it might be just what we need.   - Okay.
继续往里走
Go on in.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
行了  小卡  我们应该放松一下
Oh, come on, Cam, we deserve this.
好了  你先进去
All right, you get started,
热一下身  我马上就来
and then I'll jump in when it starts to heat up.
米奇尔
Mitchell!
快来  不然我要把你扔进去了
Come on. Then I will throw you into it, tiger.
来嘛来嘛
Rub a dub dub.
天哪  不
Dear, no.
朗翰姆
Langham.
你们两个都来吗
Both of you?
那好吧
Huh. Well, okay.
不  不  不  不好
No. No. No, not okay.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
你把房卡给我了
You gave me your room key.
什么
What?!
别装的这么吃惊
Don't act so shocked.
你在单身派对的时候跟我说
You told me at the bachelor party
你们两个有各自的生活
you two lead separate lives.
你去单身派对了
You went to the bachelor party?
是的  然后我开始为自己的行为内疚
Yes, and I was starting to feel bad about sneaking around,
但现在看来是我多虑了
but I guess I shouldn't have,
现在我明白你有什么打算了
Now that I see what you're up to.
我什么打算也没有
I'm not up to anything!
我是不小心遗落了房卡
I left my key by mistake.
我们显然都很焦躁
We're all obviously tense.
让我们都深呼吸一下
Let's take a deep breath...
进来浴缸里
Get in the tub...
没可能的
That's not happening.
你想跟我说一下
You want to tell me
你是如何"不小心"把房卡给了别人吗
how you "Accidentally" gave someone your key?
那你想跟我说一下你一整天是如何
You want to tell me why you spent all day
从某个男人的肚脐上喝龙舌兰酒的吗
sipping tequila out of some guy's navel?
你看见了
You saw that?
我猜的
I guessed.
伙计们  出了什么事
Hi, guys. What's going on?
克莱尔  你能等下再来吗
Hey, Claire. Can you please just come back?
我们正在吵架
We're in the middle of an argument.
我猜我知道原因
Oh. Bet I know why.
你们还要进来泡澡吗
Are you guys getting in the bath?
也许我猜错了
Or I'm way off.
朗翰姆
Langham!
是蒂姆  不能让他知道我在这
It's Tim.He can't know I'm here.
他有非常严重的信任问题
He has insane trust issues.
非常严重
Insane?
朗翰姆  你在里面吗
Langham, are you in there?
-从这个门出去  -在这里
- Go out this door.  - In here.
歌洛莉亚  快点好吗
Gloria, hurry up, will you?
他就要上来了
He's on his way up.
我要刮胡子
I need to shave.
你来啦
Oh, you're here.
我是杰・普里契特
Jay Pritchett.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for stopping by.
浴袍不错
Nice robe.
像《重回昨日》里那个何夫
Like Hef, Back In The Day.
我就有话直说了
I'm gonna cut to the chase.
我喜欢你的生活方式
I like your lifestyle.
我也想感受一下
I want a taste of it.
当然  我很荣幸  但是
Well, s-sure, that's flattering, but...
好吧  浴室是你的了
Okay, the bathroom is all you--
歌洛莉亚  这位是伯特・坦纳
Gloria, it's Burt Tanner!
那才不是伯特・坦纳
That's not Burt Tanner,
那是朗翰姆
that's Long-ham.
朗翰姆
Langham!
那玩意在这里干什么
What's that thing doing here?
享用一杯马天尼酒
Just enjoying a dirty martini
只为在那浴室中荡涤嬉闹
before a cleansing romp in the bath.
我不是为这位准备的沐浴
That's not who the bath is for.
我搞错了
Oh, my mistake.
欢迎您  克莱尔
Welcome...Claire.
[Claire有"洁净"的意思]
过了今晚
You're certainly gonna be clean
你一定会洁净如初的  不是吗
by the end of the night, aren't you?
杰  我的护发品都忘带了
Jay, I forgot all my hair products!
我去和克莱尔借一下
I'm going to borrow from Claire.
好  安全了
Okay, the coast is clear.
杰
Jay!
快走  快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
菲尔  你在这里啊
Hey. Phil, there you are.
德奇  你怎么知道我在哪里
Ducky! How'd you know where I was?
这座城市由魔法师掌管
Magicians run this town.
真的吗
Really?
才不是  我是高级尊贵层的修面管家
No. I'm a shaving butler up on plus.
今天发生的事情让我感到很抱歉
Look, I felt bad about how things went down today,
所以我想过来再给你一次机会
and I-I just wanted to give you another shot.
这边请
Right this way.
我真的觉得你会喜欢我的表演
I really think you're gonna like what you see.
先让我布置一下
Okay, let me just get everything set up.
破茧成蝶
Metamorphosis.
人们说唯一不变的是变化
They say the only constant is change.
不好意思  那个是啥
I-I'm sorry, what -- I-- s-- what is that?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't even know.
可能是我老婆买的东西
Something my wife bought.
我来把它拿走  开始
Let me just get rid of it. Here we go.
不是吧  又触动人家没有老婆的痛处
Really, uh, rubbing it in on that wife thing, huh?
破茧成蝶
Metamorphosis.
伯特
Burt!
非常高兴你能从楼上降阶相见
Nice of you to come down a floor
来看看底层人民是怎么生活的
and see how the other half lives.
如果你愿意
If you will,
请帮我把它提过头顶  在我手腕处收紧
raise it above my head and pinch it at my wrists.
只管系紧扎好
Go ahead and make it good and tight.
不用给我放水
Don't be easy on me.
好了
Okay.
现在
Now...
就像小小的橡树子成长为参天大树那样
as the lowly caterpillar becomes the majestic butterfly,
卑微的毛毛虫变成了壮丽的蝴蝶
as the tiny acorn becomes the mighty oak,
于是  我们完成了
so, too, do we complete our...
破茧成蝶
metamorphosis.
所以这只是虚张声势的把戏而已
So, it's the Governor's Bluff.
不  这可是对虚张声势的极大改善
Well, it's a huge twist on the Governor's Bluff.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no!
这里还有其他的元素
There were other elements.
你把我弄慌了
You just kind of threw me off.
我都忘了  我本应该
I forgot -- I was gonna --
华丽丽地出场  我应该用一个
as a flourish I was gonna use one --
太赞了
A-- that's amazing!
你用这种
Y-you lull me with this--
快捷变装迷惑我
- with this hacky quick change,
与此同时
and the whole time,
却把一只狗模型变成了火辣女佣
you're changing the fake dog into a hot maid?
太有才了  这才是魔术
It's brilliant! It's magic!
不  那叫做破茧成蝶
No, that's metamorphosis!
和你一样  伯特
Like you, Burt,
我享受更上乘的东西
I enjoy the finer things.
事实上
As a matter of fact,
那可能是我为你定的古巴货到了
that's probably the Cuban I ordered for you.
小卡  要是你想要一场单身派对
Cam, if you wanted a bachelor party,
你早说就好了嘛
you should have just said something.
我是在到这里以后  才知道我想要的
Well, I didn't know I wanted one until we got here.
可你却一直这样叹气
And you're so "Eh, eh, eh,"
-我都不敢说什么  -好吧
- I-I was afraid to say anything.   - Okay, all right.
对于你们俩  幸运的是
Lucky for the two of you,
我比你们自己更了解你们
I know you better than you know yourselves,
而你俩所需要的是一点点
and what the two of you need
具有罪恶感的小乐趣
is a little guilty pleasure,
或者我可以称之为...
or should I say...
先生  您让我留意的苏格兰快递到了
The Scotch delivery you had me on the lookout for, sir.
我喜欢你的作风  普里契特
I like your style, Pritchett.
你入围了
You're in.
维加斯
Vegas.
这让我想起了我过世的爷爷
This reminds me of my late grandfather.
他是苏格兰人吗
He was Scottish?
他是脱衣舞男
He was a stripper.
好了
There we go.
孩子  你手艺不错
You've got the touch, kid.
我有幸继承了我母亲的小手  先生
I was blessed with my mother's small hands, sir.
我可以为您点一个免费赠送的
Shall I order your complimentary,
室内魔石按摩吗
in-room, hot-stone massage?
免费赠送的吗
Complimentary?
全都属于您高级贵宾体验之内的  先生
All part of the excelsior-plus experience, sir.
您先在私人健身泳池中泡一会儿再做更好
Might be nice after a dip in your private lap pool.
我从前怎么都没享受过这个
Oh, where has this been all my life?
我在电梯里看到一个竖琴师
You know, I saw a harpist in the elevator.
我们明天早午餐时可以让他过来演奏么
Can we get that for our brunch tomorrow?
要是我说了算肯定行  但是很遗憾
If it was up to me, yes, but unfortunately,
那是我们尊享极致会员的专属项目
that is reserved for our excelsior-ultra guests only.
62  63  64层
62, 63, 64!
你妹
Son of a bitch!